Harrison S. Morris Papers, 1784-1970 (bulk 1895-1935 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1879-1948; 121.0 boxes
  - Subseries 2A: General, 1885-1948; 101.0 boxes
    - Vonnoh, Robert William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Vorst, Marie von, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Vose, Nathaniel M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Vose, Robert C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - The Voters' League, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Wager & Karpeler, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Wager-Smith, Curtis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Wagner, Anne Leonard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Wagner, Emilie O., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Wagner, General Louis Junior High School, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Wagner, J. C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Wagner, John & Sons, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Wagner-Taylor Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Wagner Tree Institute--Sam Wagner see subseries 9EE, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Waite, Emily Burling, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - [folder omitted], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Walbridge, Charles Charter, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Walcott, Dr., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Walden, Lionel, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Walker, Etheridge, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Walker, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Walker, Jeannette, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Walker, Joseph & Sons, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Walker, Laura M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Walker, Margaret C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Walker, Thomas J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Walker, W. F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Wallace, Charles William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Waller, Berthe H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Wallerstein, David, dates not examined; 2.0 folders (Folder 24-25)
    - Waln, Charlotte M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Walnut Sutton & Faught, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Walnut, T. Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - The Walpole Society, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - [Walsh] Brothers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Walsh, Charles Harper, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Walsh, Henry Collins, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Walsh, R. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Walsh, Thomas, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Walver, Martha, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - [folder omitted], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - [folder omitted], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Walter, Warner, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Walton, John, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Wanamaker, John see John Wanamaker, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Wanamaker, Rodman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Wangerheim, Mrs. Julius, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Wanger, Irving P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Wangl, Frederick, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - War Welfare Council of Philadelphia & Vicinity, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Ward, Aaron, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Ward's National Science Establishment, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Ware, Manan, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Warner, Katherine, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Warner, Lydia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Werner, Mary C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Warren, Edward, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Warwick, Charles K., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Warwick Ivan & Steele Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Washburn, Frank, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Washburn, J. D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Washburn, Watson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Washington, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - The Washington Herald, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Washington Park City Committee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Washington Park on the Delaware, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Washington Party see Progressive Party, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Washington Party, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Wavenough, Anna C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Watkins, S. C. G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Watraus, Harry see National Academy of Design, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Watrough, Mrs. Edwin H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Watson, Catering Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Watson, Mrs. Edward W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Watson, F. D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Watson, G. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Watt, Marjorie B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Watts, Harvey M. see subseries 9FF, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Watts, J. Murray, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35a)
    - Waugh, Frederick J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Waugh, Ida, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Wayland, Francis M. G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Wayne, Charles Stokes, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Wayne, Hulda H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Wayne Iron Works, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Wayne, Joseph, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Weaver, C. E. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Weaver, John, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Webb, Marvin E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Weber, F. & Company, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Webster, Lina [West], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Weeden, C. E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Weekly Review, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Weeks, Edwin Lord, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Weeks, James H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Weil, Mathilde, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Weir, J. Alden, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Weiss, Frederick, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - The Welcome Society of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 55)
    - Weld, Crew & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 56)
    - Welfare Federation, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 57)
    - Wells, Francis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 58)
    - Wells, John H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 59)
    - Wells-Lloyd Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Welsbach Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Welsh Brothers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Welsh, Francis Ralston, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Welsh, H. Devitt, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Welsh, Herbert see subseries 9HH, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Wendell, Mark, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Wendell, Miss, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Wenner, Harry C. (Wharton Wheel Company), dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Werma, H. K., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - West & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Westbrook, H. P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Westcott, Mary H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Western Union Telegraph Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Weston, Edward Payson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Weston, Harold F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Weston, Mary Melvaine, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Weston, S. Burns, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Wetherill, Anna Thorpe, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Wetherill, Mrs. Edward, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Wetmore, Edith, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Weygandt, C. N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Weygandt, Cornelius, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Weyhe, E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Wharton & Northern Railroad Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Wharton, Anna Lovering see subseries 9A, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Wharton, Anne Hollingsworth, dates not examined; 2.0 folders (Folder 2-3)
    - Wharton, Joseph see subseries 9A, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Wharton, Bromley, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Wharton, Charles W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Wharton Coal & Coke Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Wharton, Edith, 1900 July 19; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Wharton, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Wharon, Ellen Clifton, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Wharton Fisheries Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Wharton, Frances Brille, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Wharton, Frances Willing, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Wharton, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Wharton, Joseph S. Lovering, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Wharton, Mary Lawrence, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Wharton, Mary Lovering, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Wharton, N. C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Wharton, Redman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Wharton, Rosa Nielson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Wharton Ship Yard see also Wenner, Harry C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Wharton Steel Company, dates not examined; 2.0 folders (Folder 21-22)
    - Wharton, Susan P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Wharton, Thomas, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Wharton, William Moore, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Wharton, William Redwood, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Wheatley, John, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Wheatsworth Whole Wheat Crackers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Wheeler, Ginder & Crosbie, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Whicher, George M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Whipple, Dorothy, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Whipple, Henry C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Whistler, James M. see subseries 9V (Joseph Pennell), dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Whitall, John M, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - White, Andrew, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - White, Benjamin T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12a)
    - White, Caroline Carle, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - White, Charles Fred, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - White, Clarence H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - White, Esther Griffin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - White, Helene Maynard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - White, Henry C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - White, Halman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - White, J. William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - White, James T. & Company Publishers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - White, Janet P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - White, Joseph J., Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - White, Letitia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - White, Parry, Schnader & Maria, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - White, Richard P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - White, Thomas Carle, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Whiteside, Frank R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Whitman, Jay M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Whitin, Albert H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Whiting, Arthurt Battelle, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Whitlock, Brand, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Whitman, H. D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Whitman, Thelme, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Walt Whitman see subseries 9GG, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Whittelsey & Whittelsey, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Whittler Center Housing Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Whiitier Fellowship, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Who's Important in Literature, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Who's Who, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Who's Who in the Western Hemisphere, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Whosever Gospel Mission and Rescue Home, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Wicks, Edward T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Widener, Joseph, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Widener, P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Wiederseim, Grace, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Wiesv, Nina, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - "The Wife of Potiphar" play, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Wilcox James M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Wiclos, M. [W.], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Wilderstein and Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Wilenskey, Max Harris, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Wiles, Irving R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Wiley, Edwin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Wilkins, Mary, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Wilkinson, Sidney B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Willcox, Joseph, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Willcox, W. N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Willets, David, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Willet, Anne Lee and Henry Lee Willet, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Willet Studies, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Willet, Mrs. William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Williem, Edwin Rudge, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - William Gardner & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - William N. Horstmann Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - William H. Wise & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - William Harvey Miner Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - William J. Cruhler Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Wiliams, Annette, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Williams, Arthur, Jr. & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Williams, Brown & Carlk, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Williams, David, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Williams, Dwight, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Williams, Ellis D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Williams, Francis Churchill, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Williams, Francis Howard see subseries 9II, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Williams G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Williams, H. C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Williams, Fred Ballard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Williams, Henry William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Williams, J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Williams, Issac L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Williams, Jesse Lynch, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Williams, John Clarence, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Williams, Mary Beatrice, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Williams, Saul W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Williams, Sophia W. R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Williams, Talcott, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Williamson, Ada C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Williamson Free School of Mechanical Trades, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Williamson, R. N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Willing, J. Thomson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Willis, Mary B. N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Wills, B. R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Wills, George W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16a)
    - Wills, Marguerite, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Willson, Robert N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Wilmer Atkinson Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Wilmer, H. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Wilimington Art Center & Museum, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Wilson, George W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Wilson, J. C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Wilson, Margaret Woodrow, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Wilson, S. Davis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Wilson, Samuel, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Wilson, William N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Windrim, John T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Winsley, Margaret, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Winsor, Mary and Ellen Windsor, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Winston, John C. Company see John C. Winston Company, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Winters, Reihert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Wire, Marion, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Wistar & Stokes, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Wistar, Charles M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Wistar, Mrs. Thomas, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Wistar, Annis Lee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Wister, Frances Anne, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Wister House, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Wister, Jones, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Wister, Mary, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Wister Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Wister, Owen, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Wister, Sarah B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Witmer, Mrs. Lightner, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Wolf, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Wolf, Patterson, Block and Schott, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Wolfe & Adams, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Wollenstein, S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Women Suffrage Headquarters for Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Women's Democratic Club of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Woman's Hospital, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Women's City Club of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - The Women's Conference of the Society for Ethical [Culture], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Women's League for Good Government, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Women's Phil Beta Kappa Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Wood, Anna Wharton, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Wood, Charles J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - [Wood], Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Wood, N. Curtis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Wood, Horatio B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Wood, James F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Wood, L. A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Wood, Lydia Cope, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Wood, Spencer S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Wood, Stuart, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Wood, Walver, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Wood, Willliam S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Woodberry, George E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Woodbury, Charles, H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Woodbury, Herbert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - [folder omitted], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Woodman Art Gallery, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Woodruff, Clinton Rogers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Woodruff, Horan and Povan, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Woods, Matthew, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Woodward, George, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Woodworth, Lizette Memorial Association see Lizette Woodworth Memorial Association, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Wooley, M. Roberta, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Woolston, Nancy, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Wooton, Edward M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Worcester Art Museum, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - The World, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - World-Telegram, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - World War Veterans' Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - World's Fair Managers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Wortham, T. M. & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - Wright, A. F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Wright, Catherine Morris see subseries 9A, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Wright, David Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Wright, Mrs. Harrison, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Wright, Letitia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Wright, Mary, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Wright, Sidney see subseries 9A, dates not examined; 1.0 item
    - Wright, Tyndale & Van Roden, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - The Writer, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Writers Press Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Wyeth, Charles M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Wyeth, Newell Converse, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Wylly, Robert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Yacht Sales & Service, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Yachtmen's Service Agency, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Yale Lock Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Yale Review, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)